inkfreezer.com 2019-03-31

# inkFreezer Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how inkFreezer uses and protects any information that you give inkFreezer when you use this website.  
inkFreezer is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
inkFreezer may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 05-03-2013.  
 **What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:  
1. We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, or respond to a survey.  
2. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
 **What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
1\. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).  
2\. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).  
3\. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
 **Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
 **How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  
 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.inkFreezer.com  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to inkFreezer and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on inkFreezer send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
inkFreezer.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. inkFreezer privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
 **Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  
 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to inkfreezer@gmail.com  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.  
 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
 **Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. The full “Google Analytics privacy policy can be viewed at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>  
**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.  
 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  
This policy was last modified on August 27, 2015  
 **Contacting Us**  
To contact the staff at inkFreezer, please consult the [contact page](http://www.inkfreezer.com/contact-us "Contact US") on our website for further instructions on how to reach us.
